https://teczcape.blogspot.com/p/privacy-policy-www.html

www.teczcape.blogspot.com
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at
tigerfish1101@yahoo.com.sg.
At www.teczcape.blogspot.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme
importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of
personal information is received and collected by
www.teczcape.blogspot.com and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many other Web sites, www.teczcape.blogspot.com makes use of log
files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (
IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ),
date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze
trends, administer the site, track users movement around the site, and
gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information
are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
www.teczcape.blogspot.com does not use cookies.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on www.teczcape.blogspot.com.
.:: Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your
users based on their visit to www.teczcape.blogspot.com and other sites
on the Internet.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the
Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL -
http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include .......
Google Adsense
Amazon
These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the
advertisements and links that appear on www.teczcape.blogspot.com send
directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address
when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or
Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure
the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the
advertising content that you see.
www.teczcape.blogspot.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.
You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party
ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as
for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.
www.teczcape.blogspot.com's privacy policy does not apply to, and we
cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual
browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with
specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.
Home
Subscribe to:
Posts (Atom)
Featured
BuzzFeed - How to Cook Fish if You Hate Cooking
BuzzFeed Food - 21 Surprising Things You can Make in a Rice Cooker
Huffingtonpost - Turn A Cheap Packet Of Instant Ramen Into A Gourmet Meal
Basil Magazine (Archived) - Traditional Congee, Modern Interpretation
Basil Magazine (Archived) - Bitter Melon, What a Melon!
bok choy/choy sum
bone "healing"
vine leaf
grain bowl (chicken)
grain bowl (plant-based)
grain bowl (seafood)
grain bowls
grains/seeds
green beans
hairy melon
HappyCall Pan (HCP)
Vegetarian
veggie bowl (chicken)
veggie bowl (plant-based)
veggie bowl (seafood)
Copyright© 2006-2019 - teczcape -
Content is original and may not be reproduced without permission.
bok choy/choy sum
bone "healing"
vine leaf
grain bowl (chicken)
grain bowl (plant-based)
grain bowl (seafood)
grain bowls
grains/seeds
green beans
hairy melon
HappyCall Pan (HCP)
Vegetarian
veggie bowl (chicken)
veggie bowl (plant-based)
veggie bowl (seafood)
zucchini
Copyright© 2006-2019 - teczcape -Content is original and may not be reproduced without permission.To reference content, link back to teczcape.Thank You.
